<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Epstein Exposed</title>
    <link>https://epstein-exposed.com</link>
    <description>Comprehensive coverage of the Jeffrey Epstein DOJ file releases. In-depth analysis of documents, emails, and court records.</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <item>
      <title>Attorney General William Barr Refused to Recuse Himself from Epstein Case Despite Family Ties - Secret DOJ Memos Expose Cover-Up</title>
      <link>https://epstein-exposed.com/william-barr-epstein-recusal-justice-department.html</link>
      <guid>https://epstein-exposed.com/william-barr-epstein-recusal-justice-department.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:38:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>DOJ files reveal AG William Barr blocked recusal demands in Epstein case despite his father's ties to the financier and conflicts of interest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's Billionaire Friend Tom Barrack Used Epstein Connections for Secret UAE Fundraising - 'He Opens Every Door'</title>
      <link>https://epstein-exposed.com/tom-barrack-epstein-trump-fundraising.html</link>
      <guid>https://epstein-exposed.com/tom-barrack-epstein-trump-fundraising.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:37:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>DOJ files reveal Trump ally Tom Barrack leveraged Epstein's network for Middle East deals and political fundraising worth millions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supermodel Naomi Campbell Used Her Children's Charity to Fund Epstein's Private Events - DOJ Files Expose Fashion World's Dark Secret</title>
      <link>https://epstein-exposed.com/naomi-campbell-epstein-charity-modeling.html</link>
      <guid>https://epstein-exposed.com/naomi-campbell-epstein-charity-modeling.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:37:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>Newly released DOJ files reveal supermodel Naomi Campbell's charity connections to Jeffrey Epstein and private modeling events.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Media Queen Oprah Winfrey's Secret Epstein Strategy Sessions: 'We Need to Control the Women's Stories'</title>
      <link>https://epstein-exposed.com/oprah-winfrey-epstein-media-empire-meetings.html</link>
      <guid>https://epstein-exposed.com/oprah-winfrey-epstein-media-empire-meetings.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:36:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>Shocking DOJ files reveal Oprah Winfrey held private meetings with Jeffrey Epstein about media strategy and victim narrative control.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ABC's George Stephanopoulos Secretly Coordinated Epstein TV Interviews: 'We Can Control the Narrative'</title>
      <link>https://epstein-exposed.com/george-stephanopoulos-epstein-abc-interviews.html</link>
      <guid>https://epstein-exposed.com/george-stephanopoulos-epstein-abc-interviews.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 11:35:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>DOJ files reveal ABC anchor George Stephanopoulos secretly helped Jeffrey Epstein plan favorable TV appearances and media strategy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Victoria's Secret Billionaire Leslie Wexner Gave Epstein 'Full Power of Attorney' Over $1 Billion Empire - Shocking DOJ Files Expose Total Control</title>
      <link>https://epstein-exposed.com/leslie-wexner-victorias-secret-epstein-power-attorney.html</link>
      <guid>https://epstein-exposed.com/leslie-wexner-victorias-secret-epstein-power-attorney.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:59:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>DOJ files reveal Leslie Wexner gave Jeffrey Epstein complete control over his Victoria's Secret fortune and personal life decisions worth over $1 billion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blackstone CEO Stephen Schwarzman's Secret Epstein Investment Calls: 'The Opportunities Are Extraordinary'</title>
      <link>https://epstein-exposed.com/stephen-schwarzman-blackstone-epstein-connections.html</link>
      <guid>https://epstein-exposed.com/stephen-schwarzman-blackstone-epstein-connections.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:58:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>DOJ files reveal private equity titan Stephen Schwarzman discussed lucrative investments with Jeffrey Epstein in newly released phone records</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harvard Law Professor Alan Dershowitz's Secret $300K Epstein Retainer: 'I Need You to Handle This Quietly'</title>
      <link>https://epstein-exposed.com/alan-dershowitz-epstein-legal-advice.html</link>
      <guid>https://epstein-exposed.com/alan-dershowitz-epstein-legal-advice.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:58:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>DOJ files reveal Harvard's Alan Dershowitz received $300,000 from Epstein for 'special legal consultation' in confidential arrangement.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexican Billionaire Carlos Slim's Secret Epstein Telecom Deals: 'The Infrastructure Project Needs Your Touch'</title>
      <link>https://epstein-exposed.com/carlos-slim-epstein-telecom-empire.html</link>
      <guid>https://epstein-exposed.com/carlos-slim-epstein-telecom-empire.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:57:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>DOJ files reveal Mexican telecom mogul Carlos Slim's hidden business relationship with Jeffrey Epstein involving major infrastructure deals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Co-Founder Sergey Brin's Secret Epstein Meetings: 'We Need to Discuss the Algorithm Changes'</title>
      <link>https://epstein-exposed.com/sergey-brin-epstein-google-meetings.html</link>
      <guid>https://epstein-exposed.com/sergey-brin-epstein-google-meetings.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 09:56:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>Shocking DOJ files reveal Google co-founder Sergey Brin held multiple private meetings with Jeffrey Epstein to discuss AI and search algorithm modifications.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Martha Stewart's Secret Epstein Hamptons Parties: 'The Girls Will Love Your Garden' - Shocking DOJ Files Reveal Lifestyle Empire's Dark Side</title>
      <link>https://epstein-exposed.com/martha-stewart-epstein-hamptons-parties.html</link>
      <guid>https://epstein-exposed.com/martha-stewart-epstein-hamptons-parties.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:59:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>DOJ files expose Martha Stewart's secret coordination with Jeffrey Epstein for exclusive Hamptons parties featuring young women and powerful guests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kevin Spacey Hosted Secret Film Screenings at Epstein's Manhattan Mansion - DOJ Files Expose Hollywood's Dark Ties</title>
      <link>https://epstein-exposed.com/kevin-spacey-epstein-private-screenings.html</link>
      <guid>https://epstein-exposed.com/kevin-spacey-epstein-private-screenings.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:59:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>DOJ files reveal Kevin Spacey organized private movie screenings at Jeffrey Epstein's NYC mansion for A-list celebrities and financiers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Media Mogul Rupert Murdoch's Secret Epstein Strategy Calls Revealed in DOJ Files</title>
      <link>https://epstein-exposed.com/rupert-murdoch-epstein-media-empire.html</link>
      <guid>https://epstein-exposed.com/rupert-murdoch-epstein-media-empire.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:58:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>Explosive DOJ files reveal Rupert Murdoch held private calls with Jeffrey Epstein about media coverage and reputation management strategies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Magician David Blaine Performed Private Shows for Epstein's High-Profile Guests - DOJ Files Reveal Celebrity Entertainment Network</title>
      <link>https://epstein-exposed.com/david-blaine-epstein-magic-shows.html</link>
      <guid>https://epstein-exposed.com/david-blaine-epstein-magic-shows.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:57:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>DOJ files reveal magician David Blaine performed exclusive shows at Jeffrey Epstein's properties for VIP guests including foreign dignitaries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woody Allen Had 'Standing Dinner Invitations' at Epstein's Manhattan Mansion - New Files Reveal Regular Visits</title>
      <link>https://epstein-exposed.com/woody-allen-epstein-dinners.html</link>
      <guid>https://epstein-exposed.com/woody-allen-epstein-dinners.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 09:56:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>DOJ files reveal Woody Allen was a regular guest at Jeffrey Epstein's Manhattan mansion with 'standing dinner invitations' arranged by staff.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Morgan Stanley CEO James Gorman's Secret Epstein Meetings: Wall Street's Hidden Scandal</title>
      <link>https://epstein-exposed.com/morgan-stanley-james-gorman-epstein-meetings.html</link>
      <guid>https://epstein-exposed.com/morgan-stanley-james-gorman-epstein-meetings.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 16:39:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>DOJ files reveal Morgan Stanley CEO James Gorman met with Jeffrey Epstein multiple times for 'business discussions' - exclusive details exposed</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaire Glenn Dubin's Wife Eva Let Epstein Live in Their Home After Prison - Shocking Family Ties Exposed</title>
      <link>https://epstein-exposed.com/glenn-dubin-epstein-family-ties.html</link>
      <guid>https://epstein-exposed.com/glenn-dubin-epstein-family-ties.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 16:38:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>DOJ files reveal billionaire Glenn Dubin's wife Eva allowed Jeffrey Epstein to stay in their family home after his 2008 prison release.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hyatt Hotels Heir Thomas Pritzker's Secret Epstein Business Deals Exposed in DOJ Files</title>
      <link>https://epstein-exposed.com/thomas-pritzker-hyatt-epstein-connections.html</link>
      <guid>https://epstein-exposed.com/thomas-pritzker-hyatt-epstein-connections.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 16:37:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>DOJ files reveal Hyatt Hotels billionaire Thomas Pritzker had extensive business dealings with Jeffrey Epstein, including real estate investments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LinkedIn Founder Reid Hoffman's $2 Million Mystery: Secret Epstein Donations Exposed</title>
      <link>https://epstein-exposed.com/reid-hoffman-linkedin-epstein-donations.html</link>
      <guid>https://epstein-exposed.com/reid-hoffman-linkedin-epstein-donations.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 16:36:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>DOJ files reveal LinkedIn founder Reid Hoffman secretly funneled $2 million through Epstein to MIT - then tried to cover it up when scandal broke.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former Israeli PM Ehud Barak's Secret Epstein Meetings: 'I Need to See You Urgently'</title>
      <link>https://epstein-exposed.com/ehud-barak-epstein-meetings.html</link>
      <guid>https://epstein-exposed.com/ehud-barak-epstein-meetings.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 16:35:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>DOJ files reveal urgent messages between former Israeli Prime Minister Ehud Barak and Jeffrey Epstein, including secret Manhattan meetings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apollo CEO Leon Black Paid Epstein $158 Million for 'Tax Advice' - DOJ Files Reveal Shocking Details</title>
      <link>https://epstein-exposed.com/leon-black-apollo-payments.html</link>
      <guid>https://epstein-exposed.com/leon-black-apollo-payments.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 16:25:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <description>Billionaire Leon Black paid Jeffrey Epstein $158 million over five years for alleged tax and estate planning advice, new DOJ documents reveal.</description>
    </item>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://epstein-exposed.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>

    <item>
      <title>"What Day Will Be the Wildest Party?" Elon Musk's Desperate Texts to Epstein Exposed</title>
      <link>https://epstein-exposed.com/musk-epstein-emails</link>
      <guid>https://epstein-exposed.com/musk-epstein-emails</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>The world's richest man spent years trying to score an invite to Epstein's private island—and the receipts are mortifying. Buried in the 3.5 million pages are at least 16 emails between Musk and the convicted pedophile.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Steve Bannon Got a Free Apple Watch, Private Planes, and Hundreds of Texts from Epstein</title>
      <link>https://epstein-exposed.com/bannon-epstein-texts</link>
      <guid>https://epstein-exposed.com/bannon-epstein-texts</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Trump's former strategist was chatting up the sex trafficker right until weeks before his death—and Epstein knew exactly what he had on them both.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Commerce Secretary Lutnick Brought His Kids to Epstein's Island on a Yacht</title>
      <link>https://epstein-exposed.com/lutnick-yacht-island</link>
      <guid>https://epstein-exposed.com/lutnick-yacht-island</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2026 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Howard Lutnick's story just completely fell apart. Emails show his wife coordinated a Christmas visit on their 188-foot yacht—seven years after he claims he stopped associating with Epstein.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>The Dinner Party: Prince Andrew, Woody Allen, Katie Couric—All at Epstein's House</title>
      <link>https://epstein-exposed.com/prince-andrew-dinner</link>
      <guid>https://epstein-exposed.com/prince-andrew-dinner</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>A December 2010 email reveals the disgraced royal was staying at the convicted pedophile's Manhattan mansion while A-listers were invited over for dinner.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>"32 Plane Trips": The Clinton-Epstein Connection in Black and White</title>
      <link>https://epstein-exposed.com/clinton-plane-trips</link>
      <guid>https://epstein-exposed.com/clinton-plane-trips</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Internal emails show Epstein's team tracking and discussing the former president's extensive flight history on the "Lolita Express."</description>
    </item>

  </channel>
</rss>
