<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Epstein Exposed</title>
    <link>https://epstein-exposed.com</link>
    <description>Comprehensive coverage of the Jeffrey Epstein DOJ file releases. In-depth analysis of documents, emails, and court records.</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://epstein-exposed.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>

    <item>
      <title>&quot;Bring Your Harem!&quot;: Richard Branson's Emails to Epstein Exposed</title>
      <link>https://epstein-exposed.com/richard-branson-harem</link>
      <guid>https://epstein-exposed.com/richard-branson-harem</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Virgin billionaire invited Jeffrey Epstein to his private island with a shocking request—and offered PR advice on how to spin his crimes.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Google's Founders and Ghislaine Maxwell: The Dinner Invitations They Can't Explain</title>
      <link>https://epstein-exposed.com/sergey-brin-google-maxwell</link>
      <guid>https://epstein-exposed.com/sergey-brin-google-maxwell</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Sergey Brin offered to bring Eric Schmidt to Epstein's townhouse. Maxwell called it &quot;happily casual and relaxed.&quot; New documents reveal Google's uncomfortable Epstein connection.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Peter Thiel Appears in Thousands of Epstein Documents: Lunches, Investments, and a Michelin-Star Buyout</title>
      <link>https://epstein-exposed.com/peter-thiel-thousands-documents</link>
      <guid>https://epstein-exposed.com/peter-thiel-thousands-documents</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>The PayPal co-founder's name appears thousands of times in the DOJ release. Documents reveal years of lunch meetings, a $40 million investment connection, and an exclusive Palo Alto dinner.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>NFL Owner Josh Harris Confirmed at Epstein's &quot;Intimate&quot; Bill Gates Breakfast</title>
      <link>https://epstein-exposed.com/josh-harris-gates-breakfast</link>
      <guid>https://epstein-exposed.com/josh-harris-gates-breakfast</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>New emails show the billionaire sports owner attended a private breakfast with Bill Gates at Epstein's Manhattan home. &quot;Yes very much. Thank you for inviting me.&quot;</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Epstein Paid for Dr. Oz's Travel in 2004, Files Reveal</title>
      <link>https://epstein-exposed.com/dr-oz-epstein-travel</link>
      <guid>https://epstein-exposed.com/dr-oz-epstein-travel</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>A transaction report shows Jeffrey Epstein paid $1,592 for the celebrity doctor's travel. Oz now runs Medicare and Medicaid Services under the Trump administration.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>"What Day Will Be the Wildest Party?" Elon Musk's Desperate Texts to Epstein Exposed</title>
      <link>https://epstein-exposed.com/musk-epstein-emails</link>
      <guid>https://epstein-exposed.com/musk-epstein-emails</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>The world's richest man spent years trying to score an invite to Epstein's private island—and the receipts are mortifying. Buried in the 3.5 million pages are at least 16 emails between Musk and the convicted pedophile.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Steve Bannon Got a Free Apple Watch, Private Planes, and Hundreds of Texts from Epstein</title>
      <link>https://epstein-exposed.com/bannon-epstein-texts</link>
      <guid>https://epstein-exposed.com/bannon-epstein-texts</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Trump's former strategist was chatting up the sex trafficker right until weeks before his death—and Epstein knew exactly what he had on them both.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Commerce Secretary Lutnick Brought His Kids to Epstein's Island on a Yacht</title>
      <link>https://epstein-exposed.com/lutnick-yacht-island</link>
      <guid>https://epstein-exposed.com/lutnick-yacht-island</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2026 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Howard Lutnick's story just completely fell apart. Emails show his wife coordinated a Christmas visit on their 188-foot yacht—seven years after he claims he stopped associating with Epstein.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>The Dinner Party: Prince Andrew, Woody Allen, Katie Couric—All at Epstein's House</title>
      <link>https://epstein-exposed.com/prince-andrew-dinner</link>
      <guid>https://epstein-exposed.com/prince-andrew-dinner</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>A December 2010 email reveals the disgraced royal was staying at the convicted pedophile's Manhattan mansion while A-listers were invited over for dinner.</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>"32 Plane Trips": The Clinton-Epstein Connection in Black and White</title>
      <link>https://epstein-exposed.com/clinton-plane-trips</link>
      <guid>https://epstein-exposed.com/clinton-plane-trips</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Internal emails show Epstein's team tracking and discussing the former president's extensive flight history on the "Lolita Express."</description>
    </item>

  </channel>
</rss>
